fantasticfurniture.com.au 2019-09-11

# Privacy Policy | Fantastic Furniture

## **Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy sets out how Fantastic Furniture Pty Limited (ABN 66 003 688 855) ("we", "us, "our") uses, discloses and protects any personal information about yourself that we collect when you use this website and otherwise interact with us.  You can be assured that the information collected will only be held, used or disclosed in accordance with this privacy policy. 

We may make changes to this privacy policy from time to time (without notice to you) that are necessary for our business requirements or the law. This privacy policy was last updated on August 2018. We encourage you to visit this site form time to time to ensure that you have read our most current privacy policy.

 **What we collect**

We may collect and hold the following personal information from customers, business contacts, suppliers, franchisee applications people seeking employment and other individuals with whom we deal:

  * name and contact information including email address, postal and/or delivery address and telephone number (if supplied by you);
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests;
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers; and
  * employment history and qualifications (if you apply for employment with us).

 **What we do with the information we collect and hold**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the below reasons.

  * to process your transaction and deliver products to you;
  * for internal record keeping;
  * to improve our products and services;
  * for warranty repairs on our products;
  * unless you ask us not to, we may send promotional material, from time to time, to any contact details you provide to us, about our new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting;
  * to contact you by email, SMS, phone, fax or mail for market research purposes, from time to time; and
  * to customise the website according to your interests.

We will only use your personal information as reasonably necessary for the above purposes, unless we have your permission or are required by law to otherwise handle your information (such as to respond to an emergency). Fantastic Furniture Pty Ltd may disclose your personal information for the above purposes to the following people and entities:

  * our parent corporation Fantastic Holdings Limited, its subsidiaries and their franchisees (the "Fantastic Group");
  * our franchisees, contractors and service providers (including IT services, mailing houses, shipping and distribution services and recruitment services) and those of the Fantastic Group;
  * our business associates;
  * third-party product repair partners;
  * if you choose to apply for any credit facility in connection with a purchase (where offered), the credit provider;
  * our professional advisers, such as our lawyers, accountants and auditors;
  * your employees, agents and representatives (if you are our business contact);
  * your referees (if you have applied for employment with us);
  * if any entity wishes to purchase part or whole of our business, that entity; and
  * government and regulatory authorities, and other parties if required or permitted by law.

We require these organisations to be bound by appropriate confidentiality obligations and take reasonable steps to ensure that they are aware of their privacy obligations with respect to the protection of your information. 

We do not otherwise sell or provide your information to third parties.  We will may disclose your personal information to countries overseas, in the United States of America.

 **Third Party Analytics**

We use third party application tracking services such as Google Analytics, Hotjar and FullStory to help understand the use of our Services and Site(s). Information collected by Google is governed by [Google's Privacy Policy [https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/]](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). We use the tools Hotjar and FullStory (the Tools) to, amongst other things, analyse the activities of visitors to this website, understand how our users interact with our products and services and personalise your experience. Hotjar's and FullStory’s authorised use of cookies and other tracking technologies enable them to have access to personal information or potential personal identifiable information of visitors to this website. In addition, FullStory may use third-party cookies to aid in implementing security controls and payment processing. These cookies do not track the same user across unrelated domains. The Tools do not capture any personal information entered into any input form on our website, including but not limited to names, email addresses, address information or payment information. Such access to and use of personal information by Hotjar is governed by [Hotjar’s Privacy Policy [https://www.hotjar.com/privacy]](https://www.hotjar.com/privacy) and [FullStory’s Privacy Policy [https://www.fullstory.com/legal/privacy/]](https://www.fullstory.com/legal/privacy/).

 **Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the personal information we collect about you. These measures include access controls to our premises and account based controls and internet firewalls for electronic data that we hold. Our staff and related personnel are only permitted to access information necessary for their duties.

 **How we use cookies**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. The file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets us know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to optimise the continuity of your browsing session by gathering and remembering information about your browsing preferences, including browser type, version and language, operating system, pages viewed, page access times and the referring website address. If you log in for shopping purposes, cookies will assist with remembering your shopping cart contents and log in details.

Cookies cannot be used to identify you and will not give us access to your personal information (other than the information you have chosen to share with us). We only use cookies internally for the purposes of analysing data about webpage traffic and improving our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. The data is removed from the system after it is used in this way.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

 **Controlling your personal information**

You may choose to restrict the collection, storage, use or disclosure of your information in the following ways:

  * whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes,
  * if you have previously agreed to us using your information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by:
    * writing to the Privacy Officer, Fantastic Furniture Pty Limited, PO Box 445 Chester Hill NSW 2162;
    * phoning +61 (02) 8717 2600 (during normal business hours), or 
    * e-mailing us at customercare@fantasticfurniture.com.au.
  * we mainly communicate with you through email. If you wish to unsubscribe to direct marketing communication, you can locate and click on the unsubscribe link in each of the promotional emails and we will opt you out from the mailing listing without any cost.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect, out of date, irrelevant or incomplete, please contact us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect. 

You may request access to any personal information we hold about you by contacting us. If we refuse access, we will provide you with reasons for the refusal and the relevant provisions of the Privacy Act that we rely on to refuse access. We may recover reasonable costs of retrieving information when you make an access request.

 **Complaints**

If you have any question, concerns or complaints about this privacy policy, or our use of your information, please contact us using any of the above methods. You can also contact us if you believe that the privacy of your information has been compromised or is not adequately protected. Once a complaint has been lodged, we will respond to you within 28 days, although we may request further information for the purpose of considering your complaint. If we will take longer than 28 days to investigate your complaint, we will advise you of the likely response time.

Updated August 2018
